Rebecca Rebel

PROFILE

An attentive and well-educated financial professional who has two years' experience. Works well on teams and independently. Combines mathematical and analytical skills with written and verbal communication ability. Capable of identifying cost-saving opportunities, then recommending and implementing them.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Junior Finance Specialist

Tri-State Solutions, New Haven, CT | July 2018 - Present

- Identify and cancel redundant subscription services, resulting in \$250 of monthly savings so far
- Support project managers by analyzing and revising budgets
- Research current market conditions and identify potential disruptions
- Pay vendors and reconcile client accounts
- Prepare finance-focused after-action reports for senior employees at the conclusion of projects

Financial Intern

Hartford Industries, Hartford, CT | March 2018 - May 2018

- Completed the company's shadowing program, which involved assisting a financial analyst
- Messaged and followed up with clients to inquire about payments
- Researched different financing options for a \$2,000,000 real estate purchase
- Modeled impact of proposed local tax changes
- Reviewed income statements and identified discrepancies

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Business Operations

Durham Business University, Durham, NC September 2012 - June 2016

Master of Science in Financial Data

Connecticut School of Finance, New Haven, CT September 2016 - June 2018

KEY SKILLS

- Communicating in meetings and through channels such as Microsoft Outlook and Teams
- Explaining high-level financial concepts for managers, executives and stakeholders
- Use of Microsoft Excel, Oracle Essence and Jirav business-planning software
- Report generation

CERTIFICATIONS

 Certified Excel Specialist, Microsoft Training University, 2019